Christmas Wonderland is a tv movie, romance film directed by Sean Olson.
Heidi, who initially left her small town of Pleasant Valley with the dream of one day becoming a
successful painter, has put her own art on hold to excel as an art gallery curator.
Now, a week before the gallery’s big Christmas party, she
must return home to watch her niece and nephew.
She comes face to face with her high school love, Chris, now a teacher, and offers
to help him find a new last-minute location for the Christmas dance.
Heidi Nelson, played by Emily Osment.
Chris Shepherd, played by Ryan Rottman.
Julia, played by Kelly Hu.
Tom Westwood, played by Jacob Buster.
Katie Westwood, played by Trinity Roberts.
Megan Westwood, played by Sarah Jackson.
Alice In Wonderland is a 2010 American Gothic dark fantasy adventure film directed by Tim Burton
from a screenplay written by Linda Woolverton and produced by Walt Disney Pictures.
The film stars Mia Wasikowska in the live-action role, Johnny Depp, Anne Hathaway, Matt Lucas, Helena Bonham Carter, and Crispin Glover, and features the
voices of Alan Rickman, Stephen Fry, Michael Sheen, Timothy Spall, Christopher Lee, Paul Whitehouse, Barbara Windsor and Michael Gough.
A live-action adaptation and remake of Lewis Carroll's works, the film follows Alice Kingsleigh, a nineteen-year-old who falls down a rabbit hole by going back to Wonderland, and
alongside the Mad Hatter helps restore the White Queen to her throne by fighting against the Red Queen and the Jabberwocky, a dragon who endangers Wonderland's residents.
Alice in Wonderland began development in December 2007, when Burton was asked to
direct two 3D films for Disney, including the remake of Frankenweenie.
Production began in September 2008 concluding within three months, and
was shot in the United Kingdom and the United States.
It was followed by an extensive post-production and visual effects process
where filming included live-action and motion-capture sequences.
Burton's frequent collaborator, Danny Elfman, composed an original theme for the film,
which premiered in London at the Odeon Leicester Square on February 25, 2010.
It was released in the United Kingdom and the United States through the Disney Digital 3-D,
RealD 3D, and IMAX 3D formats as well as in standard theaters on March 5.
The film generated over $1.025 billion in ticket sales and became the fifth highest-grossing film
during its theatrical run, and it is also the second-highest-grossing film of 2010.
Amongst Disney's live-action adaptations, the film is tied for third-most-expensive,
alongside Mulan and the fourth-highest-grossing readaptation to date.
It received three nominations at the 68th Golden Globe Awards
including for Best Motion Picture – Musical or Comedy.
At the 83rd Academy Awards, it won Best Art Direction and Best
Costume Design, and was nominated for Best Visual Effects.
The film received numerous other accolades.
While not the first film in its genre, Alice in Wonderland is credited with starting a trend of
live-action fairy tale and fantasy films being green-lit, particularly from Walt Disney Studios.
A follow-up film, titled Alice Through the Looking
Glass, was released on May 27, 2016.
The film explores themes of small town, holiday,
high school sweetheart, christmas.
The tone is emotional.